(Leonard:)Uh-huh.
(Penny:)We're going to Disneyland
and ride the Matterhorn.
(Leonard:)How does that involve air travel?
(Penny:)We're going to Disney World
and ride the Matterhorn.
(Howard(on the phone):)-No.
-Okay, sweetie, this started out fun...
(Penny:)...but I'm over it.
(Leonard:)We're going to Switzerland
to see the CERN Super Collider.
(Leonard:)And ski. We'll also go skiing.
(Penny:)-We're going skiing in Switzerland?
-You'll ski, I'll fall.
(Leonard:)But, yeah, we will be in Switzerland
for Valentine's Day.
-Oh, my God, Leonard, that's incredible.
-Ha-ha-ha.
SHELDON:
Not so fast.
You might wanna hold off
on lighting your Rääbeliechtli, Penny.
My ribee-what-ly?
Rääbeliechtli, it means turnip light...
...and refers to a lantern
hand-carved from a root vegetable...
...to celebrate Swiss festivals
which you'll not be celebrating...
(Sheldon:)...because, A,
these festivals occur in the fall...
(Leonard:)...and B,
you will not be going to Switzerland.